Inventaris van het archief van de Griffie Interparlementaire Betrekkingen van de Tweede Kamer der Staten-Generaal, 1945-1994
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Griffie Interparlementaire betrekkingen, A.
  - Consultative Assembly, A.1
    - Stukken betreffende het Committee on Agriculture, 1959 - 1975.; 149-166; 16 pakken en 2 omslagen
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting, 162
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting, 163
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 164
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1973, 24e zitting, 165
      - vergaderstukken, 1973 - 1975, 25e-26e zitting, 166
    - Stukken betreffende het Committee on Population and Refugees, 1959 - 1975.; 167-177; 9 pakkenen 2 omslagen
      - Special Representative's Advisory Committee, synchronisation and harmonisation of census operations in Council of Europe countries', vergaderstukken met bijlagen, 1964, 167; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Migrant Workers, vergaderstukken, 1966 - 1968 en 1970, 17e-20e en 22e zitting, 168; omslag
      - vergaderstukken, 1959 - 1962, 11e-13e zitting, 169
      - vergaderstukken, 1962 - 1964, 14e-15e zitting, 170
      - vergaderstukken, 1964 - 1966, 16e-17e zitting, 171
      - vergaderstukken, 1966 - 1968, 18e-19e zitting, 172
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting, 173
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1971, 21e-22e zitting, 174
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 175
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1974, 24e-25e zitting, 176
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1975, 26e zitting, 177
    - Stukken betreffende het Legal Committee, 1959 - 1975.; 178-223; 34 pakken 12 omslagen
      Vanaf 1968: Legal Affairs Committee
      - Sub-Committee no. 4, Frontier Formalities, 1959 - 1960, 11e-12e zitting, 178
      - Sub-Committee no. 6, Liability of Hotelkeepers, 1960, 11e-12e zitting, 179
      - Sub-Committee no. 8, Minorities, 1960 - 1961, 12e zitting, 180
      - Sub-Committee no. 10, Penal Reform, 1960 - 1964, 11e-15e zitting, 181
      - Sub-Committee no. 10, Questions of Criminal Law and Criminology, 1964 - 1968, 16e-20e zitting, 182
      - Sub-Committee no. 12, Human Rights, 1960 - 1962, 12e-13e zitting, 183
      - Sub-Committee no. 12, Human Rights, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting, 184; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 14, International Sales, 1960, 11e zitting, 185
      - Sub-Committee no. 14, Law of International Sales and Related Questions, 1965, 17e zitting, 186; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 15, Programme of Future Work, 1959 - 1964, 11e-15e zitting, 187
      - Sub-Committee no. 16, European Register of Companies, 1961, 13e zitting, 188
      - Sub-Committee no. 17, Industrial Property, 1961 - 1963, 13e-15e zitting, 189
      - Sub-Committee no. 18, Arbritation, 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting, 190
      - Sub-Committee no. 19, Agricultural Property Law, 1966 - 1967, 18e-19e zitting, 191; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 20, Uniform Interpretation of Treaties, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting, 192; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 21, Uniform Regulations on Oil and Gas Pipelines, 1967, 18e-19e zitting, 193; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 23, Holy Places, 1968, 20e zitting, 194
      - Sub-Committee no. 24, Human Rights and Mass Communications, 1968, 20e zitting, 195; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Drug Addiction, 1970 - 1972, 21e-22e zitting, 196; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Human Rights, 1969 - 1974, 21e-25e zitting, 197
      - Sub-Committee on Marine Resources and Sea Pollution, 1969 - 1970, 21e-22e zitting, 198; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Questions of Penal Law and Criminology, vergaderstukken, 1973, 25e zitting, 199; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Questions of Penal Law and Criminology, vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1971, 21e-23e zitting, 200; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on the Programme of Future Work, 1964 - 1971 en 1973, 16e-21e en 23e-24e zitting, 201
      - Sub-Committees on Northern Ireland, 1971 - 1972, 23e-24e zitting, 202; omslag
      - joint Sub-Committee of the Legal Committee and the Committee on the Budget on a European Civil Service, 1968 - 1973, 20e-22e en 24e-25e zitting, 203
      - joint Sub-Committee of the Legal Committee and the Committee on the Budget on a European Civil Service, 1959 - 1962 en 1970 - 1973, 11e-13e en 24e-25e zitting, 204
      - meeting with the Ombudsmen and Parliamentary Commissioners in Council of Europe member States, 1974, Parijs, 205
      - vergaderstukken, 1959 - 1961, 11e-12e zitting, 206
      - vergaderstukken, 1961 - 1964, 13e-15e zitting, 207
      - vergaderstukken, 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting, 208
      - vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting, 209
      - vergaderstukken, 1966 - 1967, 18e zitting, 210
      - vergaderstukken, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting (1), 211
      - vergaderstukken, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting (2), 212
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting (1), 213
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting (2), 214
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting (1), 215
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting (2), 216
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting (1), 217
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting (2), 218
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 219
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1973, 24e zitting, 220
      - vergaderstukken, 1973 - 1974, 25e zitting, 221
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1975, 26e zitting, 222
      - working group on the Extra Territorial Application of Anti-Trust Legislation, 1966, 18e zitting, 223; omslag
    - Stukken betreffende het Social Committee, 1959 - 1975.; 224-252; 22 pakken en 7 omslagen
      Vanaf 1968: Committee on Social and Health Questions
      - Group of Independent Experts on Leisure, 1961, 13e zitting, 224
      - Group of Independent Experts on Leisure, 1965 - 1967, 17e-18e zitting, 225; omslag
      - Sous-Comite de Securite et d'Hygiene Industrielles, 1970, 226; omslag
      - Sub-Committee for the 50th anniversary of the International Labour Organisation, 1968, 20e zitting, 227; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 1, Development Areas, 1959, 1964 - 1966, 11e en 16e-17e zitting, 228
      - Sub-Committee no. 2, European Social Charter, 1959 - 1960, 11e zitting, 229
      - Sub-Committee no. 3, Leisure, 1960 - 1963 en 1965, 12e-15e en 17e zitting, 230
      - Sub-Committee no. 4, Future Work, 1961, 13e zitting, 231
      - Sub-Committee no. 5, Youth Problems, 1961 - 1963, 13e-14e zitting, 232
      - Sub-Committee no. 6, Public Health, 1962 - 1966, 15e-17e zitting, 233
      - Sub-Committee on 4th and 5th seminar on International Voluntary Service, 1971 - 1974, 22e-26e zitting, 234; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Drug Addiction, 1970 - 1972, 21e-22e zitting, 235; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on the 2nd symposium of members of Parliament, Specialists in Public Health, 1970 - 1971, 236
      - Sub-Committee on the 2nd symposium of members of Parliament, Specialists in Public Health, 1965 - 1966, 237
      - Sub-Committee on the European Code of Social Security, 1971 - 1974, 23e-26e zitting, 238; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on the European Social Charter, 1972 - 1974, 24e en 26e zitting, 239; omslag
      - joint Sub-Committee on Social Problems in European Development Areas, 1960, 12e zitting, 240
      - vergaderstukken, 1959 - 1962, 11e-13e zitting, 241
      - vergaderstukken, 1961 - 1963, 12e zitting, 242
      - vergaderstukken, 1962 - 1964, 14e-15e zitting, 243
      - vergaderstukken, 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting, 244
      - vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting, 245
      - vergaderstukken, 1966 - 1967, 18e zitting, 246
      - vergaderstukken, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting, 247
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting, 248
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting, 249
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting, 250
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 251
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1975, 24e-26e zitting, 252
    - Vergaderstukken van het Committee of Chairmen to consider requests from International Non-Governmental Organisations for Consultative Status, 11e zitting, 1960.; 253; 1 omslag
    - Vergaderstukken van het Bureau of the Assembly, 12e-24e zitting, 1960 - 1974.; 254; 1 pak
      Met hiaten.
    - Stukken betreffende het Economic Committee, 1960 - 1975.; 255-290; 31 pakken en 5 omslagen
      Vanaf 1968: Committee on Economic Affairs and Development.
      - Sub-Committee no. 2, Channeltunnel Project, vergaderstukken, 1960, 12e zitting, 255; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 2, European Energy Problems, vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1968, 16e-19e zitting, 256
      - Sub-Committee no. 3, Transport and Communicaations, vergaderstukken, 1964 en 1968, 16e en 19e-20e zitting, 257; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 4, Development of Africa, vergaderstukken, 1959 - 1960 en 1962 - 1963, 11e en 13e-15e zitting, 258; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 4, Science and Economic Growth, vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1967, 17e-18e zitting, 259; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 5, European Energy Problems, vergaderstukken, 1960 - 1963, 12e-15e zitting, 260
      - Sub-Committee no. 6, Effects of European Economic Integration on the European Trade of Non-member Countries, vergaderstukken, 1959 - 1960 en 1960, 11e-12e en 14e zitting, 261; omslag
      - Sub-Committee no. 7, Road Safety, 1960 - 1962, 11e-14e zitting, 262
      - Sub-Committee no. 8, Cival Aviation, 1963 - 1964, 15e zitting, 263
      - round table 'Aid and Development, the Role of the Multilateral Organisations', vergaderstukken, 1971, 23e zitting, 264
      - vergaderstukken, 1960, 11e zitting, 265
      - vergaderstukken, 1960, 12e zitting (1), 266
      - vergaderstukken, 1960 - 1961, 12e zitting (2), 267
      - vergaderstukken, 1961, 13e zitting (1), 268
      - vergaderstukken, 1961 - 1962, 13e zitting (2), 269
      - vergaderstukken, 1962, 14e zitting (1), 270
      - vergaderstukken, 1962 - 1963, 14e zitting (2), 271
      - vergaderstukken, 1963, 15e zitting (1), 272
      - vergaderstukken, 1963 - 1964, 15e zitting (2), 273
      - vergaderstukken, 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting (1), 274
      - vergaderstukken, 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting (2), 275
      - vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting, 276
      - vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting (1), 277
      - vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting (2), 278
      - vergaderstukken, 1966 - 1967, 18e zitting (1), 279
      - vergaderstukken, 1966 - 1967, 18e zitting (2), 280
      - vergaderstukken, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting, 281
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting (1), 282
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting (2), 283
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting, 284
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting (1), 285
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting (2), 286
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 287
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1973, 24e zitting, 288
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1974, 25e zitting, 289
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1975, 26e zitting, 290
    - Vergaderstukken van het Committee on the budget, 1960 - 1975.; 291-293; 3 pakken
      - 1960 - 1965, 11e-16e zitting, 291
      - 1965 - 1970, 17e-21e zitting, 292
      - 1970 - 1975, 22e-26e zitting, 293
    - Vergaderstukken van de Working party on Reactivation of the Council of Europe, 13e zitting, 1961.; 294; 1 omslag
    - Stukken betreffende het Cultural and Scientific Committee, 1961 - 1966.; 295-308; 12 pakken en 2 omslagen
      - Committee of Cultural Experts, 17th session, Committee on coordination of Youth Activities, 1961, 295
      - Committee of Cultural Experts, 2nd meeting of the Restricted Committee, 1961, 60e zitting, 296
      - European Conference on the Preservation and Development of Ancient Buildings and Historical and Artistic Sites, 1963 - 1964, 63e-64e zitting, 297; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Films and Television, 1963, 15e zitting, 298
      - Sub-Committee on Publications, 1963, 15e zitting, 299
      - Sub-Committee on Scientific and Technological, 1966, 18e zitting, 300; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Scientific, 1961 - 1962, 13e zitting, 301
      - Sub-Committee on Scientific, 1964 - 1966, 16e-17e zitting, 302
      - Sub-Committee on Youth Questions, 1961, 13e zitting, 303
      - vergaderstukken, 1961 - 1962, 13e zitting, 304
      - vergaderstukken, 1962 - 1963, 14e zitting, 305
      - vergaderstukken, 1963 - 1964, 15e zitting, 306
      - vergaderstukken, 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting, 307
      - vergaderstukken, 1965 - 1966, 17e zitting, 308
    - Permanent working party on Parliamentary and Public Relations, vergaderstukken, 1963 - 1971.; 309-318; 10 pakken
      - 1963 - 1964, 15e zitting, 309
      - 1964 - 1965, 16e zitting, 310
      - 1964 - 1966, 17e zitting, 311
      - 1966 - 1967, 18e zitting, 312
      - 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting (1), 313
      - 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting (2), 314
      - 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting (1), 315
      - 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting (2), 316
      - 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting (1), 317
      - 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting (2), 318
    - Vergaderstukken van de Joint Working Party, 1964 - 1968.; 319-322; 4 pakken
      - Fresh Water Pollution in Europe, 1964 - 1966, 16e-17e zitting, 319
      - Youth Questions / joint meeting on Youth, 1964 - 1967, 16e-19e zitting, 320
      - Regional Planning, 1965 - 1966, 17e-18e zitting, 321
      - Regional Planning, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting, 322
    - State of signatures and ratifications of the European Establishment Convention, 1967.; 323; 1 omslag
    - Symposium on Press and other Medio of Mass Communication, 1967.; 324; 1 omslag
    - Stukken betreffende het Committee on Science and Technology, 1967 - 1977.; 325-350; 17 pakken en 9 omslagen
      - European Joint Committee on Scientific co-operation, vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1975, 23e-26e zitting, 325
      - Research group on Biological Effects of Cosmic Rays at the Altitude of Supersonic Air Transpor, 1972 - 1973, 24e-25e zitting, 326; omslag
      - Study group on Auroral Ionosphere, vergaderstukken, 1972, 23e zitting, 327; omslag
      - Study group on Glaciology, vergaderstukken, 1971, 22e zitting, 328
      - Study group on Medical Data Processing, vergaderstukken, 1972, 23e zitting, 329; omslag
      - Study group on Separation and Detection Technics in Bioscience, vergaderstukken, 1973 - 1974, 24e-25e zitting, 330; omslag
      - Study group on Space Physiology, vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 331; omslag
      - Study group on the Rhine Valley Water Table/Groundwater, vergaderstukken, 1973 - 1974, 24e-26e zitting, 332
      - Study group on the creation of a European coordinating Committee of European Private Associations in the field of Environment, 1973 - 1974, 25e zitting, 333; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Data Processing, vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1974, 23e-26e zitting, 334
      - Sub-Committee on Data Processing, vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1970, 19e-22e zitting, 335
      - Sub-Committee on Science and Parliament, ad-hoc Committee on the Organisation of the 3rd and 4th Parliamentary and Scientific Conference, vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1974, 21e-26e zitting, 336
      - Working party EFRAC, European working party for Fraction, Separation, Concentration and Detection in Bioscience, vergaderstukken 1974, 25e-26e zitting, 337; omslag
      - Working party on Aerospace Physiology and Medicine, 1972 - 1977, 24e-29e zitting, 338
      - Working party on European Polar Research, Antartica Programme, vergaderstukken 1971 - 1974, 22e-25e zitting, 339
      - Working party on Geodynamics, vergaderstukken 1971 - 1974, 22e-26e zitting, 340; omslag
      - Working party on Space Biophsics, vergaderstukken 1970 - 1975, 22e-26e zitting, 341
      - general information for the working parties of Aerospace Physiology and Medicine, Space Biophysics, Polar Research and Geodynamics, 1972, 24e zitting, 342; omslag
      - vergaderstukken, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting, (1), 343
      - vergaderstukken, 1967 - 1968, 19e zitting, (2), 344
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting, 345
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting, 346
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting, 347
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 348
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1974, 24e-25e zitting, 349
      - vergaderstukken, 1974, 26e zitting, 350
    - Committee on Parliamentary and Public Relations, 1967 - 1991.; 351-365; 12 pakken en 3 omslagen
      - Joint Committee Parliamentarians NGO Liaison Committee, 1982 - 1984, 34e en 35e zitting, 351; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Europe Day, 1983 - 1984, 35e zitting, 352; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Information Police, 1981, 33e zitting, 353; omslag
      - vergaderstukken, 1968 - 1969, 20e zitting, 354
      - vergaderstukken, 1969 - 1970, 21e zitting, 355
      - vergaderstukken, 1970 - 1971, 22e zitting, 356
      - vergaderstukken, 1971 - 1972, 23e zitting, 357
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1973, 24e zitting, 358
      - vergaderstukken, 1973 - 1974, 25e zitting, 359
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1975, 26e zitting, 360
      - vergaderstukken, 1980 - 1981, 32e zitting, 361
      - vergaderstukken, 1981 - 1982, 33e zitting, 362
      - vergaderstukken, 1982 - 1983, 34e zitting, 363
      - vergaderstukken, 1983 - 1987, 35e-38e zitting, 364
      - vergaderstukken, 1987 - 1991, 39e-42e zitting, 365
    - Stukken betreffende het bijwonen van het Symposium on Human Rights and Mass Communications te Salzburg, 1968 - 1971.; 366; 1 pak
    - Report of the European Commission of Human Rights betreffende de 'The Greek Case', 1968 - 1972.; 367-368; 2 pakken
      - vergaderstukken 1968 - 1972, 367
      - eindrapport 1972, 368
    - Informatieteksten van de Assembly, 1968 - 1974.; 369-372; 4 pakken
      - 1968, 369
      - 1969, 370
      - 1970, 371
      - 1971 - 1975, 372
    - Vergaderstukken van het Special Committee on the Intergovernmental Workprogramme of the Council of Europe, 20e-22e en 24e-25e zitting, 1968 - 1974.; 373; 1 pak
    - Stukken betreffende het Committee on Culture and Education, 1968 - 1975.; 374-379; 2 pakken en 4 omslagen
      - Sub-Committee for the Creation of a European Tele University, 1971, 23e zitting, 374
      - Sub-Committee on Historical and Artistic Monuments and Sites, 1968 - 1971, 20e-23e zitting, 375
      - Sub-Committee on Monuments and Sites, 1972 - 1974, 24e-26e zitting, 376
      - Sub-Committee on Youth Questions, 1968 - 1974, 20e-26e zitting, 377
      - vergaderstukken, 1972 - 1974, 24e zitting, 378; pak
      - vergaderstukken, 1973 - 1975, 25e-26e zitting, 379; pak
    - Overleg over de Exchange of views between the delegation of the Assembly and the Latin American Parliament te Bogota, 1969.; 380; 1 omslag
    - Overleg van de Commission du Reglement, 1969.; 381; 1 omslag
    - Vergaderstukken en correspondentie van het Committee of Senior Officials, in charge of preparations for the European Conference of Ministers responsible for regional planning, 1969 - 1970.; 382; 1 pak
    - Stukken betreffende het bijwonen van het Symposium on the Exploration and Exploitation of the Sea-bed and its Subsoil te Straatsburg, 1970.; 383; 1 pak
    - European Economic Unification and its implications for Canada, 1971.; 384; 1 pak
    - Stukken betreffende het tweede Symposium on the co-ordination of Rearch Concerning the legal systems of the countries of Central and Eastern Europe te Straatsburg, 1971.; 385; 1 omslag
    - Vergaderstukken van het Committee on European Non-member Countries, 23e-26e zitting, 1971 - 1974.; 386; 1 pak
    - Vergaderstukken van het Joint Sub-Committee on the Budget and Legal Affairs Committee on a European Civil Service, 24e zitting, 1973.; 387; 1 omslag
  - Parliamentary Assembly, A.2
    - Committee on Population and Refugees, 26e-28e zitting, 1974 - 1977.; 388; 1 pak
    - Vergaderstukken van het Committee on Parliamentary and Public Relations, 1974 - 1980.; 389-393; 5 pakken
      - 1974 - 1976, 26e-27e zitting, 389
      - 1976 - 1979, 28e zitting, 390
      - 1977 - 1978, 29e zitting, 391
      - 1978 - 1979, 30e zitting, 392
      - 1979 - 1980, 31e zitting, 393
    - Vergaderstukken van het Legal Affairs Committee, 1974 - 1980.; 394-408; 5 pakken en 10 omslagen
      - Organising Committee for the Symposium on the Future of Democratic Institutions in Europe, vergaderstukken, 1975, 26e zitting, 394
      - Organising Committee for the conference on the Development of Democratic Institutions in Europe, 1975, 27e zitting, 395
      - Sub-Committee for the Workprogramme, 1979, 30e zitting, 396
      - Sub-Committee on Enviroment Law, 1977 - 1979, 29e-30e zitting, 397
      - Sub-Committee on Fundamental Social Rights, 1977, 29e zitting, 398
      - Sub-Committee on Human Right, 1976 - 1980, 28e-31e zitting, 399
      - Sub-Committee on Questions of Penal Law and Criminology, 1977, 29e zitting, 400
      - Sub-Committee on Terroism in Europe, 1979, 31e zitting, 401
      - Sub-Committee on the Law of the Sea, 1977 - 1979, 29e-31e zitting, 402
      - Sub-Committee on the Programme of Work, vergaderstukken, 1975, 26e zitting, 403
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1976, 26e-27e zitting, 404; pak
      - vergaderstukken, 1976 - 1977, 28e zitting, 405; pak
      - vergaderstukken, 1977 - 1978, 29e zitting, 406; pak
      - vergaderstukken, 1978 - 1979, 30e zitting, 407; pak
      - vergaderstukken, 1979 - 1980, 31e zitting, 408; pak
    - Committee on Social and Health Questions, 1974 - 1986.; 409-423; 11 pakken en 4 omslagen
      - Sub-Committee Parliamentary Hearing on Genetic Engineering, 1981, 33e zitting, 409; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on International Voluntary Service, 1978 - 1979, 30e-31e zitting, 410
      - Sub-Committee on the 6th seminar on International Voluntary Service, 1975 - 1978, 26e-29e zitting, 411
      - Sub-Committee on the European Code of Social Security, 1975 - 1976, 26e-28e zitting, 412; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on the European Code of Social Security, 1978 - 1979, 30e zitting, 413; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on the European Social Charter, 1974 - 1977, 26e-29e zitting, 414
      - Sub-Committee on the Hearing Health and Solidarity, 1983, 34e zitting, 415; omslag
      - Sub-Committees on Employment in Europe, 1983 - 1984, 34e-35e zitting, 416
      - Sub-Committees on the European Social Charter and on the European Code of Social Security, 1978 - 1983, 30e-32e en 34e zitting, 417
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1976, 26e-27e zitting, 418
      - vergaderstukken, 1976 - 1978, 28e-29e zitting, 419
      - vergaderstukken, 1978 - 1980, 30e-31e zitting, 420
      - vergaderstukken, 1980 - 1982, 32e-33e zitting, 421
      - vergaderstukken, 1982 - 1983, 34e zitting, 422
      - vergaderstukken, 1983 - 1986, 35e-37e zitting, 423
    - Vergaderstukken van het Committee on the Budget and the Intergovernment Work Programme, 1974 - 1987.; 424-428; 4 pakken en 1 omslag
      - 1974 - 1979, 26e-30e zitting, 424
      - 1979 - 1984, 31e-35e zitting, 425
      - 1984 - 1987, 36e-38e zitting, 426
      - Sub-Committee for the European Civil Service, 1980 - 1987, 32e-38e zitting, 427
      - Sub-Committee on Information Policy, 1981 - 1984, 33e-34e zitting, 428; omslag
    - Committee on Economic Affairs and Development, 1974 - 1989.; 429-443; 14 pakken en 1 omslag
      - Sub-Committee in charge of the organisation of the Colloque on International Tax Avoidance and Evasion, 1979 - 1980, 30e-31e zitting, 429
      - Sub-Committee in charge of the organisation of the Symposium on Development Cooperation, 1978, 30e zitting, 430; omslag
      - Sub-Committee on Relations with International Organisations, 1976 - 1978, 27e-29e zitting, 431
      - Sub-Committee on Relations with International Organisations, 1979 - 1982, 30e-35e zitting, 432
      - vergaderstukken, 1974 - 1976, 26e-27e zitting, 433
      - vergaderstukken, 1976 - 1977, 28e zitting, 434
      - vergaderstukken, 1977 - 1978, 29e zitting, 435